( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .club، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
[Yooseong Villa]
[فيلا يوسونغ]
[Episode 2]
[الحلقة 2]
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
[Hyun Jin, I'm sorry.]
[هيون جين، أنا آسف.]
Do you really have to turn me into some kind of burden?
هل يجب عليك حقاً أن تجعلني عبئاً عليك؟
How are you a burden?
كيف تُشكّل عبئاً؟
I am.
أنا كذلك.
Like this thing stuck to you, weighing you down.
كأن هذا الشيء التصق بك، وأثقل كاهلك.
Hyun Jin.
هيون جين.
You already have your hands full with Woo Joo,
أنت مشغول بالفعل مع وو جو،
and you still went out of your way to make a room for me here.
ومع ذلك، بذلت جهدًا إضافيًا لتوفير غرفة لي هنا.
I'm never moving into this house.
لن أنتقل إلى هذا المنزل أبداً.
So please...
لذا من فضلك...
Just leave me alone.
اتركني وشأني.
[BS Food Acceptance Announcement]
[إعلان قبول منتجات الأغذية من شركة بي إس]
If only they'd sent it a few days earlier...
لو أنهم أرسلوها قبل بضعة أيام فقط...
Then I wouldn't have fought with my sister...
إذن لما كنتُ قد تشاجرت مع أختي...
I wouldn't have said those awful things to her...
ما كنت لأقول لها تلك الأشياء الفظيعة...
Am I a burden to you?
هل أنا عبء عليك؟
- Who said that? - You did.
- من قال ذلك؟ - أنت من قاله.
You haven't even tied the knot
لم تعقدا قرانكما بعد
and you've spent your whole life looking after me.
وقد أمضيت حياتك كلها في رعايتي.
It's not like I'm nine anymore.
لم أعد في التاسعة من عمري.
Oh, sweetie.
يا عزيزتي.
How did you grow up this fast?
كيف كبرتَ بهذه السرعة؟
Now I'm your mom and dad.
أنا الآن والدك ووالدتك.
- Really? - Yeah.
- حقاً؟ - نعم.
I might not be able to give you the very best,
قد لا أتمكن من تقديم الأفضل لك،
but I promise to give it my all.
لكنني أعدكم بأن أبذل قصارى جهدي.
So go ahead and invite as many guests as you want.
لذا تفضل وادعُ أكبر عدد ممكن من الضيوف.
Leave it to me.
اترك الأمر لي.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Mom.
أم.
We're closed.
مغلق.
Hey, clean this up.
هيا، نظف هذا المكان.
Is something wrong?
هل هناك خطب ما؟
Nothing's wrong.
لا يوجد أي خطأ.
It's just a little celebration.
إنه مجرد احتفال بسيط.
I'm finally escaping that shoebox of a studio,
أخيرًا، سأتمكن من الخروج من ذلك الاستوديو الصغير جدًا،
moving into a place where I can do whatever I want with it,
الانتقال إلى مكان أستطيع فيه أن أفعل ما أريد به،
and
و
where I can actually put holes in the walls.
حيث يمكنني بالفعل إحداث ثقوب في الجدران.
That's not it, is it?
ليس هذا هو الأمر، أليس كذلك؟
Whenever something's up
كلما حدث شيء ما
you come here with soju.
تأتي إلى هنا ومعك مشروب السوجو.
Do I?
هل أفعل ذلك؟
Remember when you got back from meeting your brother's in-laws,
أتذكرين عندما عدتِ من مقابلة أهل زوجة أخيكِ؟
you showed up with soju that time too.
لقد أحضرت معك مشروب السوجو في ذلك الوقت أيضاً.
This time it's a funeral.
هذه المرة جنازة.
I stood there
وقفت هناك
as the chief mourner for Sun Woo Jin.
بصفته المعزي الرئيسي لسون وو جين.
He was apparently such a good person
يبدو أنه كان شخصًا طيبًا للغاية
that everyone was crying talking about him.
كان الجميع يبكون وهم يتحدثون عنه.
But I couldn't shed a single tear.
لكنني لم أستطع ذرف دمعة واحدة.
How could I cry when I barely knew him?
كيف لي أن أبكي وأنا بالكاد أعرفه؟
I found out he had a kid right there at the funeral.
اكتشفتُ أن لديه طفلاً أثناء الجنازة.
A kid?
طفل؟
Yeah.
نعم.
They asked me if I was going to raise him.
سألوني عما إذا كنت سأقوم بتربيته.
Are they out of their minds?
هل فقدوا عقولهم؟
Expecting me to just shoulder that burden?
هل تتوقعون مني أن أتحمل هذا العبء وحدي؟
I've never taken care of anything
لم أهتم بأي شيء قط
besides myself,
بالإضافة إلى نفسي،
and I'm not about to start now.
ولن أبدأ الآن.
You doing alright?
هل أنت بخير؟
What's there to not be okay about?
ما الذي يدعو إلى عدم الشعور بالراحة؟
I spent more years apart from him
قضيت سنوات أكثر بعيداً عنه
than I ever spent with him.
أكثر مما أنفقته معه على الإطلاق.
But
لكن
there's one thing that's bugging me.
هناك شيء واحد يزعجني.
What's that?
ما هذا؟
I'll see you next time.
أراك في المرة القادمة.
- Yes, take care. - Thank you.
- نعم، اعتنِ بنفسك. - شكرًا لك.
Tae Hyung, it's me.
تاي هيونغ، أنا هنا.
There's something I really need to tell you.
هناك شيءٌ أريد حقاً أن أخبرك به.
I'll be waiting for your call.
سأنتظر مكالمتك.
The last person
الشخص الأخير
Sun Woo Jin called
اتصل سون وو جين
was me.
كنت أنا.
Why did he call?
لماذا اتصل؟
He said he had something important to say,
قال إنه لديه شيء مهم ليقوله،
so what was it?
إذن ما هو؟
I gave up wondering
لقد توقفت عن التساؤل
about his life ages ago.
عن حياته منذ زمن بعيد.
Of course it's raining.
بالطبع إنها تمطر.
So annoying.
مزعج للغاية.
When I
عندما
land this job at BS Food,
الحصول على هذه الوظيفة في شركة BS Food،
there's one dish I keep thinking about.
هناك طبق واحد لا يزال يشغل تفكيري.
[Work on recipes] [Ace the interview]
[العمل على وصفات الطعام] [اجتياز المقابلة بنجاح]
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I think food offers
أعتقد أن عروض الطعام
so many advantages.
مزايا كثيرة.
Ta-da.
نعم.
Come on, try it, Woo Joo.
هيا، جربها يا وو جو.
Here, say ah.
تفضل، قل آه.
Hey, Sun Woo Joo.
مرحباً، سون وو جو.
I put so much effort into this
لقد بذلت جهدًا كبيرًا في هذا الأمر.
practicing for the interview,
التدرب على المقابلة،
so please, one little bite.
لذا من فضلك، لقمة صغيرة.
Here, ah.
هنا، آه.
How is it? Good, right?
كيف حاله؟ جيد، أليس كذلك؟
Right?
يمين؟
Here, I'll give you a bigger piece with some meat.
سأقدم لك هنا قطعة أكبر تحتوي على بعض اللحم.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Come on, ah.
هيا بنا، آه.
Oh, hey.
أهلا.
What a waste.
يا له من هدر!
I don't want it.
لا أريده.
No?
لا؟
Yeah.
نعم.
- Hyun Jin. - Se Yeon.
- هيون جين. - سي يون.
Did you just give up on moving around
هل استسلمت للتو عن التنقل؟
and start living in the living room?
ونبدأ بالعيش في غرفة المعيشة؟
Look at this place...
انظر إلى هذا المكان...
And look at you two...
وانظروا إليكما...
Parenting is no joke.
تربية الأبناء ليست مزحة.
Tell me what to do. Anything.
أخبرني ماذا أفعل. أي شيء.
Should I tidy up?
هل عليّ أن أرتب المكان؟
Where'd you put your robot vacuum?
أين وضعت مكنسة الروبوت الخاصة بك؟
Got a dishwasher anywhere?
هل يوجد لديك غسالة أطباق في أي مكان؟
Is the air purifier on?
هل جهاز تنقية الهواء يعمل؟
What can I help with?
كيف يمكنني المساعدة؟
I'm great at pressing buttons.
أنا بارع في الضغط على الأزرار.
Okay, then...
حسناً، إذاً...
Could you...
يمكنك...
How's that? Feeling a bit cooler now?
كيف حالك الآن؟ هل تشعر بتحسن طفيف؟
Oh, so much better.
أوه، أفضل بكثير.
I can actually live again.
أستطيع أن أعيش من جديد.
That's a relief.
هذا مريح.
Finished.
انتهى.
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
How's the interview prep going for my company?
كيف تسير الاستعدادات للمقابلة في شركتي؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'm going to crush the BS Food interview.
سأجتاز مقابلة BS Food بنجاح باهر.
I have to get in
يجب أن أدخل
so I can raise Woo Joo right.
حتى أتمكن من تربية وو جو تربيةً سليمة.
Love that energy.
أحب هذه الطاقة.
Let me dig around at work
دعني أبحث في الأمر في العمل
and get you all the inside info on that team.
وسنقدم لك جميع المعلومات الداخلية عن ذلك الفريق.
Thanks so much.
ًشكراً جزيلا.
Oh, but here's the thing.
لكن إليك الأمر.
What?
ماذا؟
Who's going to watch Woo Joo
من سيشاهد وو جو
on interview day?
في يوم المقابلة؟
What's the problem? I can take care of Woo Joo that day.
ما المشكلة؟ يمكنني الاعتناء بـ وو جو في ذلك اليوم.
Wait, don't you have work?
لحظة، أليس لديك عمل؟
I'll kill thirty in the break room,
سأقتل ثلاثين شخصاً في غرفة الاستراحة.
another thirty at the cafe,
ثلاثون آخرون في المقهى،
then slip out
ثم انزلق للخارج
saying I need to hit the bank. I got you.
أقول إنني بحاجة للذهاب إلى البنك. فهمت.
You're the best.
أنت الأفضل.
Okay, Woo Joo.
حسناً، وو جو.
Hey.
يا.
You okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Woo Joo.
وداعاً يا جو.
Let's get you cleaned up...
دعنا نساعدك على التنظيف...
Wait, hold on...
انتظر، لحظة...
Woo Joo, this is where you go potty...
وو جو، هذا هو المكان الذي تذهبين فيه لقضاء حاجتك...
- No, no. - Don't do it there...
- لا، لا. - لا تفعل ذلك هناك...
Wrong spot.
مكان خاطئ.
- No. - Hold on tight.
- لا. - تمسك جيداً.
- This is insane.
هذا جنون.
They're only adorable every now and then.
إنهم رائعون فقط بين الحين والآخر.
Way more precious
أكثر قيمة بكثير
from a distance.
من مسافة بعيدة.
Same goes for Woo Joo.
وينطبق الأمر نفسه على وو جو.
Hey.
يا.
Seriously, how are you planning to do this by yourself?
بصراحة، كيف تخطط للقيام بذلك بمفردك؟
Will you actually be fine?
هل ستكون بخير حقاً؟
I was only here for a bit and I'm already drained.
لم أكن هنا إلا لفترة قصيرة، وقد استنفدت طاقتي بالفعل.
I'll manage.
سأتدبر أمري.
Things should get better
الأمور ستتحسن
once my arm's healed up.
بمجرد أن يشفى ذراعي.
So
لذا
that Pimang jerk who did this to your arm
ذلك الأحمق البيمينجي الذي فعل هذا بذراعك
hasn't even called?
لم يتصل حتى؟
No conscience,
بلا ضمير،
no sense of responsibility.
لا يشعر بأي مسؤولية.
Whatever, screw him.
مهما يكن، فليذهب إلى الجحيم.
Woo Joo and I will get by
سأتدبر أنا ووو جو أمورنا
perfectly fine without him.
أنا بخير تماماً بدونه.
He's probably off living his best life somewhere.
ربما هو الآن يعيش أفضل أيام حياته في مكان ما.
So this is the look I want for the kitchen,
هذا هو الشكل الذي أريده للمطبخ،
and this is for the living room.
وهذا مخصص لغرفة المعيشة.
And over here,
وهنا،
I need the outlets completely flush with the wall.
أحتاج إلى أن تكون المقابس الكهربائية مستوية تمامًا مع الحائط.
This is where the TV and soundbar will go,
هذا هو المكان الذي سيتم فيه وضع التلفزيون وجهاز الصوت.
so I need a quad outlet.
لذا فأنا بحاجة إلى أربعة منافذ كهربائية.
That's really not an easy job.
إنها ليست مهمة سهلة على الإطلاق.
Once the TV goes up, you won't even see it.
بمجرد أن يرتفع التلفاز، لن تراه حتى.
I can't wrap my head around
لا أستطيع استيعاب الأمر
doing recessed work
القيام بأعمال متراجعة
in a place this old...
في مكان بهذا القدم...
They said it's possible if you open up the floor.
قالوا إنه من الممكن القيام بذلك إذا قمت بفتح الأرضية.
I absolutely need
أنا بحاجة ماسة
everything to look clean inside.
كل شيء يبدو نظيفاً من الداخل.
Well if you're such an expert,
حسناً، إذا كنت خبيراً إلى هذا الحد،
do it yourself then.
افعل ذلك بنفسك إذن.
If I tear up the floor like you're suggesting
إذا قمتُ بتمزيق الأرضية كما تقترح
and accidentally hit the plumbing,
وأصاب أنابيب السباكة عن طريق الخطأ،
we're looking at a flood.
نحن نواجه خطر الفيضان.
And if this unit and the one downstairs both get water damage,
وإذا تعرضت هذه الوحدة والوحدة التي في الطابق السفلي لأضرار المياه،
are you going to cover that?
هل ستغطي ذلك؟
That's exactly
هذا بالضبط
why I'm spending money
لماذا أنفق المال
to hire someone with your expertise.
لتوظيف شخص يمتلك خبرتك.
I'm already giving you a deal,
أنا أقدم لك عرضاً بالفعل،
a huge deal,
أمرٌ بالغ الأهمية،
actually the biggest deal possible,
في الواقع، إنها أكبر صفقة ممكنة.
but you keep piling on requests
لكنك تستمر في تكديس الطلبات
and I can't make any progress.
ولا أستطيع إحراز أي تقدم.
I'm begging you here.
أنا أتوسل إليك هنا.
We need this done right so we can start on the floors
نحتاج إلى إنجاز هذا العمل بشكل صحيح حتى نتمكن من البدء في أعمال الأرضيات
and tiles,
والبلاط،
and actually move in on time.
والانتقال فعلياً في الموعد المحدد.
Oh my, look at the veins on his hands.
يا إلهي، انظر إلى عروق يديه.
Gosh.
يا إلهي.
His knife skills are amazing.
مهاراته في استخدام السكين مذهلة.
What do we have here!
ما هذا الذي لدينا هنا!
The bok choy salad has a bolder seasoning,
تتميز سلطة البوك تشوي بنكهة توابل أقوى،
tailored for single folks.
مصمم خصيصاً للعزاب.
For the wild chive greens doenjang tofu pancake,
لتحضير فطيرة التوفو مع صلصة دوينجانج بالخضار البرية ،
I let the fragrance do the heavy lifting.
أترك العطر يقوم بالعمل الشاق.
And this one's
وهذا واحد
purely for show.
للعرض فقط.
Let me try some.
دعني أجرب بعضاً منها.
Of course.
بالطبع.
The cafeteria is empty because everyone's off
الكافيتريا فارغة لأن الجميع في إجازة
to taste your cooking here.
لتذوق طعامك هنا.
This crowd is double
هذا الحشد ضعف العدد المعتاد
what we had at the "Today's Meal" launch.
ما تناولناه في حفل إطلاق "وجبة اليوم".
Team 3 has topped sales three consecutive times now.
حقق الفريق الثالث أعلى المبيعات لثلاث مرات متتالية حتى الآن.
We couldn't have done it without the directors backing us.
لم نكن لنستطيع فعل ذلك لولا دعم المخرجين لنا.
Order volume has already tripled our original goal,
لقد تجاوز حجم الطلبات هدفنا الأصلي بثلاثة أضعاف بالفعل،
so we're still on for that production line expansion, correct?
إذن ما زلنا ملتزمين بتوسيع خط الإنتاج، صحيح؟
And Director Kim,
والمخرج كيم،
you're aware we've got another project in development, right?
أنت تعلم أن لدينا مشروعًا آخر قيد التطوير، أليس كذلك؟
How many projects are you running at once?
كم عدد المشاريع التي تديرها في وقت واحد؟
Doesn't that wear you out?
ألا يُرهقك ذلك؟
If you all greenlight things quickly, it's really no problem.
إذا وافقتم جميعًا على الأمور بسرعة، فلن تكون هناك مشكلة على الإطلاق.
I'll have the proposal to you
سأقدم لك الاقتراح
by three this afternoon then.
بحلول الساعة الثالثة من بعد ظهر اليوم إذن.
There you go again.
ها أنت ذا تفعلها مرة أخرى.
With you delivering winners back to back,
بفضل تحقيقك للفائزين تباعاً،
how come you keep having vacancies?
كيف تستمر لديكم وظائف شاغرة؟
That's why we're hiring someone new soon.
ولهذا السبب سنقوم بتوظيف شخص جديد قريباً.
Yeah.
نعم.
Mr. Park.
السيد بارك.
Was the whole vein display
هل كان عرض الوريد بأكمله
really necessary though?
لكن هل هذا ضروري حقاً؟
I mean, I was impressed too.
أعني، لقد أعجبت أنا أيضاً.
How'd you lock down the production line expansion on the spot,
كيف تمكنت من حسم توسيع خط الإنتاج في الحال؟
plus get the green light for the new product so effortlessly...
بالإضافة إلى الحصول على الموافقة على المنتج الجديد بكل سهولة...
Was all that showmanship intentional?
هل كان كل ذلك الاستعراض مقصوداً؟
You plan with your head,
أنت تخطط بعقلك،
but you persuade with your body.
لكنك تقنعين بجسدك.
Excuse me?
اعذرني؟
One cooking demo beats a hundred meetings.
عرض طبخ واحد أفضل من مئة اجتماع.
They never
لم يفعلوا ذلك أبداً
look at the actual documents anyway.
انظر إلى الوثائق الفعلية على أي حال.
Classic you!
أنت كلاسيكي!
- Nice work. - Great work.
- عمل جيد. - عمل رائع.
Since you'll be swamped with work again,
بما أنك ستغرق في العمل مجدداً،
I'll take care of meeting the new candidates.
سأتولى أمر مقابلة المرشحين الجدد.
Here's the list of candidates.
إليكم قائمة المرشحين.
[Park Yoon Seong] Thanks.
[بارك يون سونغ] شكراً.
[Woo Hyun Jin]
[وو هيون جين]
Yoon Seong.
يون سونغ.
[What matters more than taste is the concept!]
[الأهم من المذاق هو المفهوم!]
Oh, my baby.
يا حبيبي.
Finally in my hands.
وأخيراً أصبحت بين يدي.
[Purchase Now]
[اشتر الآن]
[Purchase Complete]
[تم إتمام عملية الشراء]
[D-Day Interview]
[مقابلة يوم النصر]
The police car comes with its sirens on.
تأتي سيارة الشرطة وهي تشغل صفارات الإنذار.
The construction needs to be done by that time.
يجب الانتهاء من أعمال البناء بحلول ذلك الوقت.
Alright, thanks.
حسناً، شكراً.
Woo Joo.
وداعاً يا جو.
Yeah.
نعم.
I'm definitely getting this job today,
سأحصل على هذه الوظيفة اليوم بكل تأكيد.
and I'm going to whip up an omakase-style feast for you.
وسأقوم بإعداد وليمة على طريقة أومكاسيه من أجلك.
Yeah, once I give Woo Joo breakfast, I'll leave...
أجل، بمجرد أن أقدم الفطور لـ وو جو، سأغادر...
I'm being dragged to Busan right now.
يتم جرّي إلى بوسان الآن.
What?
ماذا؟
Seriously, I think my boss has gone crazy.
بصراحة، أعتقد أن مديري قد جن جنونه.
I was forced to go to this food truck thing.
أُجبرت على الذهاب إلى عربة الطعام هذه.
What do I do?
ماذا أفعل؟
Should I just quit?
هل عليّ أن أستقيل؟
Or should I ask my mom for help?
أم هل يجب أن أطلب المساعدة من أمي؟
No.
لا.
I can figure this out on my own.
أستطيع أن أجد حلاً لهذا بنفسي.
Stop stressing and just focus on your trip.
توقف عن التوتر وركز فقط على رحلتك.
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جداً.
Sorry.
آسف.
[Two hours before the interview]
[قبل ساعتين من المقابلة]
[Next door]
[المنزل المجاور]
[Not home] Excuse me, I live right next door.
[ليس في المنزل] عذراً، أنا أسكن في المنزل المجاور مباشرة.
[Downstairs]
[الطابق السفلي]
Just a moment.
لحظة واحدة.
Hello, I'm Woo Joo's auntie.
مرحباً، أنا عمة وو جو.
I know who you are.
أعرف من أنت.
I've bumped into you a couple of times before.
لقد التقيت بك صدفةً مرتين من قبل.
I hate to bother you like this,
أكره أن أزعجك هكذا،
but I've got a job interview today,
لكن لدي مقابلة عمل اليوم،
and I was wondering if you could look after him
وكنت أتساءل عما إذا كان بإمكانك الاعتناء به
for a couple of hours?
لبضع ساعات؟
Oh, what should I do...
أوه، ماذا أفعل...
We're heading to my in-laws' right now.
نحن في طريقنا الآن إلى منزل أهل زوجي.
[Phone contacts]
[جهات الاتصال بالهاتف]
- Hey, Ye Eun. - What, me?
- مرحباً، يي أون. - ماذا، أنا؟
Even if I'm off today, I can't just watch a kid.
حتى لو كنت في إجازة اليوم، لا يمكنني الاكتفاء برعاية طفل.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Hey, Hyun Young.
مرحباً، هيون يونغ.
My boyfriend and I are checking out wedding venues today.
أنا وصديقي نتفقد أماكن إقامة حفلات الزفاف اليوم.
[One hour before the interview]
[قبل ساعة من المقابلة]
What do I do now...
ماذا أفعل الآن...
I'm completely stuck...
أنا عالق تماماً...
Great work today.
عمل رائع اليوم.
Let's get something refreshing.
لنحصل على شيء منعش.
Yeah, you all worked hard.
نعم، لقد بذلتم جميعاً جهداً كبيراً.
Is it a renovation or something?
هل هو تجديد أم شيء من هذا القبيل؟
I have a huge problem.
لدي مشكلة كبيرة.
There's something I need to discuss with you right away.
هناك أمرٌ أريد مناقشته معك على الفور.
I'm...
أنا...
about to give up on Woo Joo.
على وشك التخلي عن وو جو.
What?
ماذا؟
She's giving up the kid?
هل ستتخلى عن الطفل؟
Just three hours, I swear.
ثلاث ساعات فقط، أقسم بذلك.
So what you're saying is
إذن ما تقوله هو
you want me to watch the kid
تريدني أن أعتني بالطفل
while you're at your interview?
أثناء وجودك في مقابلة العمل؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I tried everything I could
لقد جربت كل ما بوسعي
to handle this myself,
لأتولى هذا الأمر بنفسي،
but nobody compares to you.
لكن لا أحد يضاهيك.
You're super responsible,
أنت شخص مسؤول للغاية،
and you and Woo Joo have amazing chemistry.
وأنتِ ووو جو تتمتعان بتناغم رائع.
More like a disaster, actually.
بل هو أشبه بكارثة في الواقع.
Hey, get off.
انزل من هنا.
- I said get off. - See?
قلتُ لك انزل. - أترى؟
Woo Joo is so attached to you.
وو جو متعلق بكِ جداً.
To be honest, if you don't mind,
بصراحة، إذا سمحت لي،
I'd love to raise Woo Joo here with you anytime.
أود أن أربي وو جو هنا معك في أي وقت.
Have you lost your mind?
هل فقدت عقلك؟
I already said I won't take care of him.
لقد قلتُ بالفعل أنني لن أعتني به.
And I'm not even his uncle.
وأنا لست عمه حتى.
Listen.
يستمع.
It's been over three years since we met,
لقد مرّ أكثر من ثلاث سنوات منذ أن التقينا،
and when a man and a woman spend two nights together,
وعندما يقضي رجل وامرأة ليلتين معاً،
words aren't necessary between them.
لا حاجة للكلمات بينهما.
Seriously, what are you saying?
بصراحة، ماذا تقول؟
None of that would've happened if your arm was fine.
ما كان ليحدث أي من ذلك لو كانت ذراعك سليمة.
That's my point.
هذا ما أقصده.
You owe me for this arm.
أنت مدين لي بثمن هذه الذراع.
My poor baby Woo Joo.
يا إلهي، طفلي المسكين وو جو.
Oh, come on.
هيا بنا.
I can barely look after him
لا أستطيع الاعتناء به إلا بصعوبة
with my arm like this,
بذراعي هكذا،
and all the other applicants
وجميع المتقدمين الآخرين
are going to walk in with both arms working.
سيدخلون وهم يستخدمون كلتا أذرعهم.
And BS apparently has amazing perks.
ويبدو أن BS لديها مزايا مذهلة.
If I miss this interview,
إذا فاتني هذا اللقاء،
what'll become of Woo Joo?
ماذا سيحل بـ وو جو؟
Raise him yourself,
قم بتربيته بنفسك،
and I'm cutting ties.
وأنا أقطع العلاقات.
You can't just cut ties whenever you want.
لا يمكنك قطع العلاقات متى شئت.
We're connected by blood.
نحن مرتبطون بالدم.
Sorry, but we don't share a single drop of blood.
معذرة، لكننا لا نتشارك قطرة دم واحدة.
But Woo Joo does.
لكن وو جو يفعل ذلك.
Plus
زائد
we've already
لقد فعلنا ذلك بالفعل
stripped together.
تم تجريدها معًا.
Stripped? When did that happen?
تم تجريده من ملابسه؟ متى حدث ذلك؟
The bubble wrap.
غلاف الفقاعات.
Be careful.
كن حذراً.
Don't let my baby get scratched.
لا تدع طفلي يتعرض للخدش.
Easy!
سهل!
There we go.
ها نحن ذا.
The bubble wrap.
غلاف الفقاعات.
Come on...
تعال...
This place belongs to Woo Joo,
هذا المكان ملك لـ وو جو،
so treat it like it's yours
لذا تعامل معه كما لو كان ملكك.
and relax.
واسترخِ.
Woo Joo, bye.
وو جو، مع السلامة.
Wait!
انتظر!
Don't you dare give him chocolate.
إياك أن تعطيه شوكولاتة.
[Self-Introduction Letter Secrets]
[أسرار كتابة رسالة التعريف بالنفس]
These photos turned out like crap.
هذه الصور خرجت بشكل سيء للغاية.
Yes, hello?
نعم، أهلاً؟
Danny.
داني.
Could you email me that document from before?
هل يمكنك إرسال ذلك المستند الذي أرسلته سابقاً عبر البريد الإلكتروني؟
It's urgent, so please do it right now.
الأمر عاجل، لذا يرجى القيام بذلك الآن.
Oh, right now...
أوه، الآن...
Yes, got it.
نعم، فهمت.
We should develop an approach based on consumer habits
ينبغي لنا تطوير نهج قائم على عادات المستهلك
across different age groups.
عبر مختلف الفئات العمرية.
People living alone tend to go for cheap and easy meals,
يميل الأشخاص الذين يعيشون بمفردهم إلى اختيار الوجبات الرخيصة والسهلة،
which means they shop at convenience stores and buy small portions online.
وهذا يعني أنهم يتسوقون في المتاجر الصغيرة ويشترون كميات صغيرة عبر الإنترنت.
[Interview Waiting Room]
[غرفة انتظار المقابلات]
Park Ji Won, Cha Young Seok, Joo Hyun Sun,
بارك جي وون، تشا يونغ سيوك، جو هيون سون،
please come in.
تفضل بالدخول.
[Interview Admission Ticket]
[بطاقة دخول المقابلة]
I wonder if Woo Joo's doing okay.
أتساءل عما إذا كان وو جو بخير.
Hey, kid.
يا فتى.
You only have to remember three things.
كل ما عليك تذكره هو ثلاثة أشياء.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
Keep calm and don't move.
حافظ على هدوئك ولا تتحرك.
Act invisible,
تظاهر بالاختفاء،
silent as a ghost, and don't move.
صامت كالشبح، ولا تتحرك.
Okay.
تمام.
Wait, did you actually get that?
لحظة، هل فهمت ذلك فعلاً؟
Let's see.
لنرى.
Oh, come on...
هيا بنا...
Is it okay for a 20-month-old to have a hamburger?
هل من المقبول أن يتناول طفل يبلغ من العمر 20 شهراً شطيرة همبرغر؟
For a 20-month-old,
بالنسبة لطفل يبلغ من العمر 20 شهرًا،
meat patties and bread are a little premature,
فطائر اللحم والخبز غير ناضجين تمامًا،
but a few French fries should be fine.
لكن القليل من البطاطس المقلية سيكون كافياً.
Well, it says too early, not that it's forbidden.
حسناً، يقول النص إنه مبكر جداً، وليس أنه ممنوع.
Okay.
تمام.
Time to introduce you to the finer things early.
حان الوقت لتعريفكم بالأشياء الراقية مبكراً.
Here.
هنا.
Give it to me!
أعطني إياه!
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
Best thing you've ever tasted, huh?
أفضل شيء تذوقته على الإطلاق، أليس كذلك؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Here, say ah.
تفضل، قل آه.
Good, right?
جيد، أليس كذلك؟
Another life-changing moment for you, huh?
لحظة أخرى غيرت مجرى حياتك، أليس كذلك؟
Dad.
أب.
Go on, have some more.
تفضل، تناول المزيد.
This is no joke.
هذا ليس مزاحاً.
For me, food serves
بالنسبة لي، الطعام يخدمني.
as a key that unlocks my memories.
كمفتاح يفتح لي ذكرياتي.
Back when I was
في ذلك الوقت كنت
[2025 First-Half BS Food Open Recruitment Interview]
[ مقابلة التوظيف المفتوحة لبرنامج بكالوريوس العلوم في الأغذية - النصف الأول من عام 2025 ]
rejected at the BS Food final interview three years ago,
رُفض طلبه في المقابلة النهائية لبرنامج بكالوريوس علوم الأغذية قبل ثلاث سنوات.
I had a kimchi pancake
تناولت فطيرة الكيمتشي
that my sister cooked for me.
التي طبختها لي أختي.
That dish holds
يحتوي هذا الطبق
a special place in my heart.
مكانة خاصة في قلبي.
Whenever it rained,
كلما أمطرت السماء،
to cheer me up,
لتشجيعي،
my sister would throw in cheese one day
أختي ستضيف الجبن يوماً ما
and corn the next.
ثم الذرة.
All of those moments
كل تلك اللحظات
are tucked away somewhere dear to me.
مخبأة في مكان عزيز على قلبي.
To me, that represents
بالنسبة لي، هذا يمثل
what happens when food carries meaning.
ماذا يحدث عندما يحمل الطعام معنى؟
Should I become part of BS Food,
هل ينبغي أن أصبح جزءًا من شركة بي إس فود؟
I hope to create products
أتمنى أن أصنع منتجات
that effortlessly evoke
التي تستحضر بسهولة
cherished memories for consumers.
ذكريات عزيزة للمستهلكين.
What's that noise?
ما هذا الصوت؟
Why is there so much noise?
لماذا كل هذه الضوضاء؟
You have no reason to be crying.
ليس لديكِ أي سبب للبكاء.
I should be the one in tears!
كان ينبغي أن أكون أنا من يبكي!
No.
لا.
Seriously...
بجد...
Mama.
ماما.
Because of you...
بسببك...
You're quiet again now that we're outside.
لقد عدتَ هادئاً الآن بعد أن خرجنا.
I want that.
أريد ذلك.
- Why are you so heavy? - Dad.
- لماذا أنت ثقيل الوزن هكذا؟ - أبي.
I want that.
أريد ذلك.
[In-law]
[في القانون]
Sweetie, you shouldn't do that.
يا عزيزتي، لا يجب أن تفعلي ذلك.
Sweetie, where'd Mommy go?
يا حبيبتي، أين ذهبت ماما؟
No.
لا.
What?
ماذا؟
Honey, over here, here!
يا حبيبتي، تعالي إلى هنا، هنا!
I can't be the only one going down.
لا يمكن أن أكون الوحيد الذي ينهار.
Now it's your turn to suffer.
حان دورك الآن لتعاني.
Honey, how was your interview?
عزيزتي، كيف كانت مقابلتك؟
What the hell.
يا للهول!
Come on.
تعال.
Honey?
عسل؟
Are you insane? Why would you come here?
هل أنت مجنون؟ لماذا أتيت إلى هنا؟
You're unbelievable, you liar.
أنت لا تصدق، أيها الكاذب.
Well,
حسنًا،
I couldn't walk into an interview wearing a cast.
لم أستطع دخول مقابلة عمل وأنا أرتدي جبيرة.
I just removed it
لقد قمت بإزالته للتو
for a little bit.
لفترة قصيرة.
That's just how things work.
هكذا تسير الأمور.
Whatever.
أيا كان.
Take him back.
أعده إلى المنزل.
Are you crazy?
هل أنت مجنون؟
You're calling me crazy
أنت تصفني بالجنون
instead of saying thank you?
بدلاً من قول شكراً؟
No, I'm asking if you're out of your mind.
لا، أنا أسألك إن كنت مجنوناً.
How did you watch him?
كيف كنت تراقبه؟
And look at the mess you made at the company...
وانظر إلى الفوضى التي أحدثتها في الشركة...
I'm a victim here too.
أنا ضحية هنا أيضاً.
My personal sanctuary is now
ملاذي الشخصي الآن
destroyed property and mental trauma.
تدمير الممتلكات والصدمات النفسية.
Take him, now.
خذوه الآن.
Wait, I need to grab some diapers first.
انتظر، أحتاج إلى إحضار بعض الحفاضات أولاً.
Just take him.
خذه معك.
I said wait a minute!
قلت انتظر لحظة!
You can handle the diaper situation yourself.
يمكنكِ التعامل مع مسألة الحفاضات بنفسكِ.
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
Wait, where are you going?
لحظة، إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
You're supposed to help fix this, Uncle.
من المفترض أن تساعد في إصلاح هذا يا عمي.
How many times do I have to say I'm not his uncle!
كم مرة عليّ أن أقول إنني لست عمه!
He's...
هو...
Woo Joo...
ذلك جو...
He disappeared.
لقد اختفى.
- Woo Joo. - Sweetie.
- وو جو. - حبيبتي.
Woo Joo!
يا جو!
- Sweetie, come here! - Woo Joo!
- حبيبتي، تعالي إلى هنا! - وو جو!
You go in there, hurry.
ادخل إلى هناك، أسرع.
How am I supposed to go in?
كيف يُفترض بي أن أدخل؟
You're the kid's aunt, hurry up and go in.
أنتِ عمة الطفل، أسرعي وادخلي.
Sweetie!
حبيبي!
Come here, sweetie, come here.
تعالي إلى هنا يا حبيبتي، تعالي إلى هنا.
- Woo Joo! - Where'd the baby go?
- وو جو! - أين ذهب الطفل؟
Where?
أين؟
Over there.
هناك.
Woo Joo.
وداعاً يا جو.
Seriously, let's never cross paths again.
بصراحة، دعونا لا نلتقي مجدداً.
Same goes for you, Woo Joo.
وينطبق الأمر نفسه عليك يا وو جو.
Look who's talking.
انظر من يتكلم.
Woo Joo.
وداعاً يا جو.
Your uncle...
عمك...
I mean, Sun Tae Hyung.
أقصد، سون تاي هيونغ.
What is wrong with him?
ما به؟
Did something happen today?
هل حدث شيء ما اليوم؟
What did you do? What did you eat?
ماذا فعلت؟ ماذا أكلت؟
Oh, never mind.
أوه، لا بأس.
Let's not think about him.
دعونا لا نفكر فيه.
Thanks, you caught a fish.
شكراً، لقد اصطدت سمكة.
With the baby out of my life, it's so peaceful.
بعد رحيل الطفل عن حياتي، أشعر براحة كبيرة.
Perfect.
ممتاز.
Why aren't you answering your phone?
لماذا لا تجيب على هاتفك؟
Your place is flooded right now.
مكانك غارق بالمياه الآن.
I warned you about that foundation, didn't I?
لقد حذرتك بشأن ذلك الأساس، أليس كذلك؟
The plumbing completely exploded.
انفجرت أنابيب المياه بالكامل.
If I'd been able to reach you yesterday,
لو كنتُ قد تمكنت من الوصول إليك بالأمس،
none of this would've happened.
ما كان ليحدث أي من هذا.
We lost our only chance to fix it.
لقد أضعنا فرصتنا الوحيدة لإصلاح الأمر.
Something unexpected came up yesterday
حدث شيء غير متوقع أمس
and my phone got wrecked...
وتحطم هاتفي...
I warned you this job was dangerous.
لقد حذرتك من أن هذه الوظيفة خطيرة.
So what's going to happen to my place?
إذن، ماذا سيحدث لمنزلي؟
What do you mean what happens? The work's delayed.
ماذا تقصد بما يحدث؟ العمل متأخر.
We need to wait for it to dry
علينا الانتظار حتى يجف
before anyone can start again.
قبل أن يتمكن أي شخص من البدء من جديد.
Sir.
سيد.
So when will I
متى سأفعل ذلك؟
be able to move in?
هل يمكن الانتقال إليه؟
At least another month.
شهر آخر على الأقل.
We need to wrap up
علينا أن نختتم الأمر
before the next team can come in.
قبل أن يتمكن الفريق التالي من الدخول.
Sir...
سيد...
Oh, this...
أوه، هذا...
The electrical work isn't done, so I'll come back later.
لم يتم الانتهاء من أعمال الكهرباء، لذا سأعود لاحقاً.
The walls need to be dry before we can start the wallpaper work.
يجب أن تجف الجدران قبل أن نبدأ العمل على ورق الجدران.
This is the management office. There's a leak reported downstairs.
هذا مكتب الإدارة. تم الإبلاغ عن وجود تسريب في الطابق السفلي.
Please contact me.
يرجى الاتصال بي.
[Electrical work, ten days]
[أعمال كهربائية، عشرة أيام]
[Wallpaper, ten days]
[خلفية، عشرة أيام]
[Tile, ten days]
[بلاطة، عشرة أيام]
No.
لا.
[So where am I supposed to live...]
[إذن أين من المفترض أن أعيش...]
Stop. Please stop.
توقف. من فضلك توقف.
Come on, stop.
هيا، توقف.
Stop!
قف!
Oh, no...
أوه، لا...
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Just leave it there.
اتركه هناك.
[Your delivery has been completed]
[تم إتمام عملية التسليم]
No.
لا.
With this heat and moisture...
مع هذه الحرارة والرطوبة...
my babies are going to suffer.
أطفالي سيعانون.
If that little brat
إذا كان ذلك الطفل الصغير المزعج
hadn't wrecked my phone...
لم يتلف هاتفي...
No, if that woman
لا، إذا كانت تلك المرأة
had never dumped the kid on me...
لم يسبق له أن ترك الطفل عليّ...
No!
لا!
If only we hadn't crossed paths at the funeral...
لو لم نلتقِ في الجنازة...
Actually, going back to the first family meeting...
في الواقع، بالعودة إلى أول اجتماع عائلي...
No, all the way back to Pimang...
لا، بل على طول الطريق إلى بيمانغ...
No!
لا!
I swear on my life
أقسم بحياتي
I will never deal with her again.
لن أتعامل معها مرة أخرى.
My precious babies.
أطفالي الأعزاء.
I'm going to keep my babies safe.
سأحرص على سلامة أطفالي.
Any chance I could stay one more month in the studio...
هل من الممكن أن أبقى شهراً إضافياً في الاستوديو؟
The next tenant already signed.
تم توقيع العقد مع المستأجر التالي بالفعل.
[Storage service] My piece measures 800 millimeters across.
[خدمة التخزين] يبلغ عرض قطعتي 800 مليمتر.
You'd have to book immediately,
سيتعين عليك الحجز فوراً
but the wait list is pretty long.
لكن قائمة الانتظار طويلة جدًا.
This is a tiny studio apartment. I can't fit furniture like a sofa in here.
هذه شقة استوديو صغيرة جدًا. لا أستطيع وضع أثاث مثل الأريكة هنا.
Didn't you always say your home would never betray you?
ألم تقل دائماً أن منزلك لن يخونك أبداً؟
Guess it betrayed you?
أظن أنها خانتك؟
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .club، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
All right.
حسنًا.
Keep coming.
استمروا في المجيء.
This way, this way.
من هنا، من هنا.
Okay, this way, this way.
حسناً، من هنا، من هنا.
Not that way,
ليس بهذه الطريقة،
this way!
من هنا!
Oh my, hey...
يا إلهي، مهلاً...
Oh my, the peppers, the peppers!
يا إلهي، الفلفل، الفلفل!
Stop, stop.
توقف، توقف.
Whoa, seriously,
يا إلهي، بجدية!
you're driving all over the peppers!
أنت تقود سيارتك فوق الفلفل!
These peppers are so plump and good.
هذه الفليفلة ممتلئة ولذيذة للغاية.
Whoa, seriously.
يا إلهي، حقاً.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Why did you come out here?
لماذا أتيت إلى هنا؟
Is someone moving in?
هل سينتقل أحد إلى هنا؟
Which floor are they going to?
إلى أي طابق سيذهبون؟
You know...
أنت تعرف...
As far as I know,
بقدر ما أعرف،
nobody left this morning...
لم يغادر أحد هذا الصباح...
Mom, they destroyed your peppers.
يا أمي، لقد دمروا الفلفل الخاص بكِ.
Oh my, what am I going to do?
يا إلهي، ماذا سأفعل؟
Seems like we have a new neighbor.
يبدو أن لدينا جارًا جديدًا.
Yeah.
نعم.
Oh my, look at you! Here is our Summer...
يا إلهي، انظري إليكِ! هذا هو صيفنا...
and here is Spring...
وها هو الربيع قد حلّ...
and little Autumn is here too!
وقد وصلت الخريف الصغيرة أيضاً!
It's Daddy.
إنه أبي.
Hey, Lee Jae Min.
مرحباً، لي جاي مين.
Shouldn't you be out on a delivery?
ألا يجب أن تكون في مهمة توصيل؟
You checking crypto again?
هل تتفقد العملات الرقمية مجدداً؟
Excuse me,
اعذرني،
which unit are you heading to?
إلى أي وحدة أنت ذاهب؟
Okay, go to unit 206.
حسناً، اذهب إلى الوحدة 206.
206?
206؟
Hi, Woo Joo!
مرحباً، وو جو!
- Just drop everything in the living room. - Yes.
- ضع كل شيء في غرفة المعيشة. - نعم.
Hold on,
يتمسك،
what's happening here?
ما الذي يحدث هنا؟
The baby's aunt.
عمة الطفل.
You said I'm incredibly dependable.
قلتَ إنني شخص يُعتمد عليه بشكل كبير.
You're super responsible.
أنت شخص مسؤول للغاية.
And the baby and I have incredible chemistry.
وأنا والطفل لدينا انسجام رائع.
And you and Woo Joo have amazing chemistry.
وأنتِ ووو جو تتمتعان بتناغم رائع.
And you mentioned you'd like
وذكرت أنك ترغب
to raise the baby here with me.
أن يربي الطفل هنا معي.
To be honest, if you don't mind,
بصراحة، إذا لم يكن لديك مانع،
I'd love to raise Woo Joo here with you anytime.
أود أن أربي وو جو هنا معك في أي وقت.
So you don't actually mean
إذن أنت لا تقصد في الواقع
you're moving in, do you?
أنت ستنتقل إلى هنا، أليس كذلك؟
Sure, this is Woo Joo's place,
بالتأكيد، هذا منزل وو جو.
but...
لكن...
I'm already living here.
أنا أعيش هنا بالفعل.
And why is that an issue?
ولماذا تُعتبر هذه مشكلة؟
We've
لقد
already
بالفعل
stripped
مُقشّر
down together.
انزلوا معاً.
We've already stripped together.
لقد تجردنا من ملابسنا معًا بالفعل.
Going forward,
في المستقبل،
skip the phone calls,
تجنب المكالمات الهاتفية،
just knock on the door.
ما عليك سوى طرق الباب.
I appreciate
أقدر ذلك
your cooperation.
تعاونكم.
Cooperation for what?
التعاون من أجل ماذا؟
How does any of this make sense?
كيف يمكن أن يكون أي من هذا منطقياً؟
The two of us living together?
هل سنعيش نحن الاثنان معًا؟
Then,
ثم،
do you have 5.36 million won?
هل لديك 5.36 مليون وون؟
5.36 million won?
5.36 مليون وون؟
- What are you talking about? - Damage compensation.
- ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟ - التعويض عن الأضرار.
This is the scene of the incident
هذا هو موقع الحادث
from the day
منذ اليوم
you left the baby with me and disappeared.
لقد تركت الطفل معي واختفيت.
[Seat replacement, one million] On that exact day
[استبدال المقاعد، مليون] في ذلك اليوم بالتحديد
[Carpet cleaning, one million] when you left for your interview,
[تنظيف السجاد، مليون] عندما غادرت لإجراء المقابلة،
this is the tragic evidence
هذا هو الدليل المأساوي
[Marble repair, one million won] of all the damage I suffered.
[إصلاح الرخام، مليون وون] من بين جميع الأضرار التي لحقت بي.
If you're still not convinced,
إذا لم تقتنع بعد،
here's more from that same day.
إليكم المزيد من ذلك اليوم نفسه.
On that exact day when you went to your interview,
في ذلك اليوم تحديداً الذي ذهبت فيه إلى مقابلة العمل،
thanks to the phone
بفضل الهاتف
Woo Joo wrecked,
وو جو دمر،
I missed the contractor payment and the critical window,
فاتني موعد دفع مستحقات المقاول والموعد النهائي الحرج.
which led to a complete catastrophe.
مما أدى إلى كارثة كاملة.
As a result, my move-in
ونتيجة لذلك، انتقلت إلى
was delayed by a full month.
تأخر لمدة شهر كامل.
The bill for all of this
فاتورة كل هذا
is exactly 5.36 million won.
وهو بالضبط 5.36 مليون وون.
Wait,
انتظر،
you're not seriously
أنت لا تتحدث بجدية
telling me you plan to stay here, are you?
هل تقول لي إنك تخطط للبقاء هنا؟
This is simply temporary shelter
هذا مجرد مأوى مؤقت
for myself and my babies.
لنفسي ولأطفالي.
But strictly speaking,
لكن بالمعنى الدقيق للكلمة،
we're not even related,
لا تربطنا أي صلة قرابة،
and beyond that,
وما وراء ذلك،
you're a man and I'm a woman.
أنت رجل وأنا امرأة.
Hang on,
انتظر لحظة،
do you actually view me as a man?
هل تنظر إليّ حقاً كرجل؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
You're so not my type.
أنت لست من النوع الذي يعجبني على الإطلاق.
The feeling is mutual.
الشعور متبادل.
You're simply Woo Joo's aunt to me,
أنتِ بالنسبة لي مجرد عمة وو جو،
that's all you are.
هذا كل ما أنت عليه.
Then it's settled,
إذن فقد تم الاتفاق.
we can live together just fine.
يمكننا أن نعيش معاً بشكل جيد.
No, this still isn't okay.
لا، هذا لا يزال غير مقبول.
Wait, hold on.
انتظر، تمسك.
Why am I seeking approval from you
لماذا أسعى للحصول على موافقتك؟
when someone else actually owns this place?
عندما يمتلك شخص آخر هذا المكان بالفعل؟
By your own logic,
بحسب منطقك الخاص،
the owner here isn't you,
المالك هنا ليس أنت،
it's Woo Joo.
إنه وو جو.
When I think about it,
عندما أفكر في الأمر،
at the funeral, Woo Joo was the true chief mourner.
في الجنازة، كان وو جو هو المعزي الرئيسي الحقيقي.
Which means Woo Joo is also the true owner.
وهذا يعني أن وو جو هو المالك الحقيقي أيضاً.
So, what's your take?
إذن، ما رأيك؟
Can I be your tenant?
هل يمكنني أن أكون مستأجراً لديكم؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Yes.
نعم.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
See? He said yes.
أترى؟ لقد قال نعم.
Ta-da.
نعم.
At your service, Master.
أنا في خدمتك يا سيدي.
Woo Joo, what's in your mouth?
وو جو، ما الذي في فمك؟
Please tell me that's not chocolate.
أرجوك قل لي أن هذا ليس شوكولاتة.
For breakfast today we have
تناولنا اليوم على الإفطار ما يلي:
hormone-free chicken breast,
صدر دجاج خالٍ من الهرمونات،
organic rice, locally grown cabbage,
أرز عضوي، ملفوف مزروع محلياً،
and Korean carrots.
والجزر الكوري.
Need me to continue?
هل تريدني أن أستمر؟
It's excellent for longevity.
إنه ممتاز لإطالة العمر.
This is decaf.
هذا قهوة منزوعة الكافيين.
And this is for your Vitamin D synthesis.
وهذا يتعلق بتكوين فيتامين د.
Here, here.
هنا، هنا.
Woo Hyun Jin.
وو هيون جين.
Don't fall for this.
لا تنخدع بهذا.
[Congratulations on passing the final selection]
[تهانينا على اجتياز المرحلة النهائية من الاختيار]
Woo Joo!
يا جو!
I got the BS job!
حصلت على وظيفة تافهة!
Oh, congrats.
أوه، مبروك.
Woo Joo, clap.
وو جو، صفق.
Clap.
صفق.
Give your auntie a "thumbs up".
أعطِ عمتك علامة "الإبهام لأعلى".
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
You know,
أنت تعرف،
rather than hanging around here,
بدلاً من التسكع هنا،
why not go out with your friends?
لماذا لا تخرج مع أصدقائك؟
Step outside, breathe some fresh air,
اخرج إلى الهواء الطلق، واستنشق بعض الهواء النقي.
treat yourself to something tasty.
دلل نفسك بشيء لذيذ.
Pick up some outfits for work.
اشتري بعض الملابس للعمل.
Don't worry about Woo Joo or the house.
لا تقلق بشأن وو جو أو المنزل.
Say bye, Auntie's going out.
وداعاً، خالتي ستخرج.
Woo Joo, I'll be back.
وو جو، سأعود.
Does this make any sense?
هل هذا الكلام منطقي؟
He's a man, I'm a woman,
هو رجل، وأنا امرأة.
how can we live together?
كيف يمكننا أن نعيش معاً؟
Men and women should keep their distance.
ينبغي على الرجال والنساء الحفاظ على مسافة بينهم.
Nobody's asking you to share a bed with him.
لا أحد يطلب منكِ أن تشاركيه السرير.
Why wouldn't you though?
لكن لماذا لا تفعل ذلك؟
Just be housemates, nothing more.
مجرد رفقاء سكن، لا أكثر.
Honestly, I see no problem with it.
بصراحة، لا أرى أي مشكلة في ذلك.
If anything, it's beneficial.
بل على العكس، إنه مفيد.
With childcare and chores,
مع رعاية الأطفال والأعمال المنزلية،
you can divide it all evenly.
يمكنك تقسيمها كلها بالتساوي.
Evenly?
بالتساوي؟
Not a chance.
مستحيل.
Absolutely not.
بالتأكيد لا.
Yesterday he stormed in
بالأمس اقتحم المكان
and I got caught off guard,
وفوجئت بالأمر،
but tonight I will
لكنني سأفعل الليلة
definitely kick that man out.
بالتأكيد اطرد ذلك الرجل.
All I need to do is survive one month.
كل ما علي فعله هو أن أعيش شهراً واحداً.
If I just stay on that woman's good side,
إذا حافظت فقط على علاقة جيدة مع تلك المرأة،
I can save on rent and storage,
يمكنني توفير تكاليف الإيجار والتخزين،
no problem.
لا مشكلة.
What a touching effort.
يا له من جهد مؤثر.
Signing up to be a servant just for your furniture.
التسجيل كخادم لأثاثك فقط.
Classic move from a former lackey,
حركة كلاسيكية من تابع سابق،
you really understand what people want.
أنت تفهم حقاً ما يريده الناس.
It's freezing.
الجو بارد جداً.
Not a servant, it's called strategy.
ليس خادماً، بل يُسمى استراتيجية.
It's pure paternal devotion to my babies.
إنه إخلاص أبوي خالص لأطفالي.
After those repair costs,
بعد تكاليف الإصلاح تلك،
my account's down to 153,000 won,
انخفض رصيدي إلى 153,000 وون.
and the loan payment is due soon.
ويستحق سداد القرض قريباً.
But you know how things between men and women
لكنك تعرف كيف تسير الأمور بين الرجال والنساء
can get complicated.
قد يصبح الأمر معقداً.
What if you end up
ماذا لو انتهى بك الأمر إلى
catching feelings for her?
هل بدأت مشاعرك تجاهها؟
Catch feelings? Not in a million years.
هل يمكن أن تنشأ مشاعر؟ مستحيل.
But that woman seemed really set on getting rid of you.
لكن يبدو أن تلك المرأة كانت مصممة حقاً على التخلص منك.
What if she doesn't back down?
ماذا لو لم تتراجع؟
Not going to happen.
لن يحدث ذلك.
Even fate is working in my favor.
حتى القدر يعمل لصالحي.
She...
هي...
landed a job.
حصلت على وظيفة.
Hyun Jin.
هيون جين.
You're not buying anything?
لن تشتري أي شيء؟
Let me buy you something to celebrate your job.
دعني أشتري لك شيئاً احتفالاً بوظيفتك.
No, I already have enough clothes.
لا، لديّ ما يكفي من الملابس بالفعل.
What are you reading?
ماذا تقرأ؟
I've got to find childcare for Woo Joo,
يجب أن أجد جليسة أطفال لـ وو جو،
but nannies cost over 2 million won.
لكن تكلفة المربيات تتجاوز مليوني وون.
And daycares are all backed up...
وجميع دور الحضانة تعاني من ازدحام شديد...
Gosh.
يا إلهي.
Adapting to our company at first is going to be really demanding.
سيكون التأقلم مع شركتنا في البداية أمراً صعباً للغاية.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Woo Joo and I are both
أنا ووو جو كلانا
going to need time to settle in.
سيحتاج الأمر إلى بعض الوقت للاستقرار.
You think that woman
هل تعتقد أن تلك المرأة
will actually follow your grand plan?
هل سيتبعون خطتك الكبرى بالفعل؟
Just wait and see.
انتظروا وسترون.
She'll reach out to me in less than ten minutes.
ستتصل بي في أقل من عشر دقائق.
Ten minutes.
عشر دقائق.
Tick tock tick tock...
تيك توك تيك توك...
Just consider that guy
فكر في ذلك الرجل فقط
a short-term assistant.
مساعد لفترة قصيرة.
Hire him, use him, endure him.
استأجره، استعن به، تحمله.
You hold all the power anyway.
أنت تملك كل السلطة على أي حال.
Still, something about it feels wrong.
مع ذلك، هناك شيء ما يبدو خاطئاً في الأمر.
Hyun Jin.
هيون جين.
Suppress that old-fashioned mindset of yours.
تخلص من تلك العقلية القديمة لديك.
Just think about what benefits you now.
فكر فقط في الفوائد التي ستجنيها الآن.
All right.
حسنًا.
I got a message.
وصلتني رسالة.
There's something pressing we should sort out,
هناك أمر ملحّ يجب علينا حله،
don't you think?
ألا تعتقد ذلك؟
Let's talk in the living room at seven tonight.
لنتحدث في غرفة المعيشة الساعة السابعة مساءً.
One month.
شهر واحد.
Exactly one month, no longer.
شهر واحد بالضبط، لا أكثر.
Let's do nine to six.
لنبدأ من التاسعة صباحاً حتى السادسة مساءً.
During my hours at BS,
خلال ساعات عملي في شركة BS،
I need you to look after Woo Joo completely.
أحتاج منك أن تعتني بـ وو جو تماماً.
Agreed.
متفق.
And keep the apartment tidy while you're at it.
واحرص على أن تكون الشقة مرتبة أثناء قيامك بذلك.
Just maintain things like you have been.
استمر في الحفاظ على الأمور كما كانت.
Auntie.
خالتي.
Yeah.
نعم.
Okay.
تمام.
But it's fifty-fifty.
لكن الاحتمالات متساوية.
In good conscience, as co-residents.
بضمير مرتاح، بصفتنا مقيمين مشتركين.
Agreed.
متفق.
Water, gas, electric,
الماء، الغاز، الكهرباء،
wifi included,
خدمة الواي فاي متوفرة،
all split in half.
انقسمت جميعها إلى نصفين.
Done.
منتهي.
And since Woo Joo technically owns this place,
وبما أن وو جو يمتلك هذا المكان من الناحية الفنية،
his diapers and formula
حفاضاته وحليب الأطفال
are also split evenly.
كما يتم تقسيمها بالتساوي.
Fine, agreed.
حسناً، موافق.
Agreed.
متفق.
[Roommate Agreement]
[اتفاقية السكن المشترك]
Pimang?
Pimang?
Looks like something's on it.
يبدو أن هناك شيئًا ما عليه.
No, forget it. Don't buy it.
لا، انسَ الأمر. لا تشتريه.
Pimang guy?
رجل البيمانغ؟
So you really are Woo Jin's brother?
هل أنت حقاً شقيق وو جين؟
- One random day,
- يوم عشوائي واحد،
- another "universe"
- عالم آخر
- suddenly dropped into it.
- سقطت فيه فجأة.
Mommy.
أمي.
What am I supposed to do with the baby?
ماذا أفعل بالطفل؟
We need to decide which of you will raise him.
علينا أن نقرر من منكم سيتولى تربيته.
What? You smiling?
ماذا؟ هل تبتسم؟
This is not the time to smile.
ليس هذا وقت الابتسام.
Read the room.
اقرأ الوضع.
Why did you...
لماذا فعلتَ ذلك؟
Why did you just leave the baby with me?
لماذا تركتِ الطفل معي؟
I'll raise him.
سأربيه.
I'll take care of Woo Joo.
سأعتني بـ وو جو.
Will you actually be fine?
هل ستكون بخير حقاً؟
Woo Joo and I will get by
سأتجاوز أنا ووو جو الأمر.
perfectly fine without him.
أنا بخير تماماً بدونه.
Look at this place...
انظر إلى هذا المكان...
Seriously, how are you planning to do this by yourself?
بصراحة، كيف تخطط للقيام بذلك بمفردك؟
I have to get in
يجب أن أدخل
so I can raise Woo Joo right.
حتى أتمكن من تربية وو جو تربيةً سليمة.
Your place is flooded right now.
مكانك غارق بالمياه الآن.
So when will I be able to move in?
متى سأتمكن من الانتقال؟
At least another month.
شهر آخر على الأقل.
Hold on, what's happening here?
لحظة، ما الذي يحدث هنا؟
So you don't actually mean you're moving in, do you?
إذن أنت لا تقصد أنك ستنتقل فعلاً، أليس كذلك؟
Just consider that guy a short-term assistant.
اعتبر ذلك الرجل مجرد مساعد مؤقت.
With childcare and chores, you can divide it all evenly.
مع رعاية الأطفال والأعمال المنزلية، يمكنك تقسيم كل شيء بالتساوي.
One month.
شهر واحد.
I need you to look after Woo Joo completely.
أريدك أن تعتني بـ وو جو تماماً.
Done.
تم.
Agreed.
موافق.
I appreciate your cooperation.
أقدر تعاونكم.
Make sure you knock
تأكد من أن تطرق الباب
when you need me.
عندما تحتاجني.
Hold on, you don't have work?
لحظة، أليس لديك عمل؟
How can you look after Woo Joo while I'm at work?
كيف يمكنكِ الاعتناء بـ وو جو أثناء وجودي في العمل؟
You're so useless.
أنت عديم الفائدة تماماً.
Just until I find my footing at the company.
«فقط حتى أجد مكاني في الشركة.»
Hello, I'm Park Yoon Seong, manager of Planning Team 3.
مرحباً، أنا بارك يون سونغ، مدير فريق التخطيط 3.
I really wanted Yoon Seong to only see me at my best.
كنتُ أتمنى حقاً أن يراني يون سونغ في أفضل حالاتي فقط.
- Let me have it. - No way.
- دعني آخذه. - مستحيل.
What if you end up falling for that woman?
ماذا لو وقعت في حب تلك المرأة؟
No, Woo Joo.
لا، وو جو.
No!
لا!
Oh crap.
يا إلهي!